(Raj:)Excuse me. Oh, it's my assistant, Trevor.
(Raj:)Go for Koothrappali. Uh-huh.
(Howard:)They gave him an assistant?
(Howard:)If I want a new pen,
I have to go to the bank with wire cutters.
(Sheldon(still smiling):)Have we at this point
met our social obligations?
(Leonard:)Not yet.
Okay, put it on my calendar, but start
thinking of a reason why I can't go.
(Raj:)Alrighty? Koothrappali out.
(Raj:)God bless that boy.
(Raj:)- Don't know what I'd do without him.
- You just got him this afternoon.
(Raj:)Yes, but I'm finding
that having a lackey suits me.
- A lackey?
- I'm sorry, is that politically incorrect?
(Raj:)In India, we just call them untouchables.
- Now?
- Almost.
(Raj:)Speaking of untouchables,
I've got great news for you guys.
(Raj:)People magazine is having a reception
Saturday, and I managed to get you invited.
- Oh, gee, thanks.
- Oh, you're welcome.
(Raj:)Of course, I couldn't get you
into the VIP section...
(Raj:)...because, you know, that's for VIPs,
and you guys are just, you know, P's.
(Sheldon:)There's a tribe in Papua New Guinea...